Make sure you stretch out those side muscles!
We don't want any injuries.
Remember to breathe!
One, and two, three, go!
Uh...
Don't over-exert yourself!
Not good.
Every day seems to push me closer to geriatrics.
I need to figure something out before I wind up bedridden,
with Toru in charge of my entire well-being.
Get it out of here!
Wow.
I've never seen so many massage devices in my entire life.
Cool. What's this one do?
Oh, how specific.
Uh, that one looks exciting.
This might be good as well.
Oh, look at that. How many speeds?
Is that a fishtail? They're so magical.
Ms. Kobayashi, what are these devices?
What are you going to do with them?
Uh, use them, obviously.
Are you sure about that?
When was the last time you used this pink obscenity, huh?
I will when I'm ready.
Want me to pound you?
My grandma used to love to have me pound on her shoulders like this.
There's a grandma?
Does that feel good, Ms. Kobayashi?
It's fine, I guess, but can you remove your jugs?
Huh? Let me try.
Is this a thing now?
I want to try that, too!
Ms. Kobayashi, something's on my mind that I want to talk to you about.
Hmm?
I spend a lot of my time thinking of all the ways I'd like to service you,
but I've come to realize I'm only thinking about what I want.
In order to provide the perfect service,
I need to focus on your feelings
and consider what it is you need most
or what you would like me to do for you.
Where are we going with this?
So here you go!
I know I'm not going to eat that!
How is this focusing on my feelings?
I should have known your kind heart would lead you to starve
instead of piercing my tail with your teeth.
What I wouldn't give for you to finally accept the truth about that.
Does this mean we're in a fight?
Thank you for agreeing to meet me.
I called you fools here since you work with Ms. Kobayashi every day.
Maybe don't start off by calling us fools?
Shh!
Her lower back is hurting her again.
Now that you mention it, she has been working later than usual.
Our sales tube is talented, but we work harder.
This isn't about her job, guys!
Well, there is something else I noticed.
Great! What is it?
She has really bad posture in general.
What does that have to do with her lower back hurting?
Ah, geez. Let me break it down for you.
These humans can strain their backs by hunching over their keyboards.
They can?
She should probably buy a new chair.
What?
She's been using the same old offensive office chair for years now.
I've been saying it's about time for her to treat herself to a fancy upgrade.
She says she doesn't want to pay for one.
Are they expensive?
Is Ms. Kobayashi one of those humans who buy multiples of products
because she thinks it makes them cheaper?
Yep.
She also buys well liquor and nurses it all night.
If she would eat my tail, she wouldn't have any back pain.
Whatever.
Yeah, but then her stomach would hurt.
There is something I can get from our world that could help Ms. Kobayashi with her lower back.
I'll have to go and find it.
That's, uh, maybe not a good idea.
Have you heard the story of eating the flesh of the dead?
It said if you boil the meat in a pot while visiting the underworld,
you'll become permanently trapped once you consume it.
You think I'm trying to trap her in our world?
If you did, then Ms. Kobayashi would practically be Persephone.
I don't know about Persephone.
She's more like King Dimaphone, isn't she?
Sometimes things just don't work out even when you know what's for the best.
I think I'm gonna go home and revise my strategy a bit.
You got this, Mr. Takuya? Thanks.
Huh?
I have to admit I'm impressed with your skills.
It can be hard to talk sense into Toru sometimes.
Can it?
Well, it's just logic.
Whenever emotions are heightened, it can be easy to overstep.
I was just concerned.
Mr. Takuya had a good point.
Honestly, that whole thing hit me kinda hard.
I don't see what's wrong with maximizing your power to make someone who's precious to you happy.
Isn't that what it's for?
I've always thought so.
But if Ms. Kobayashi doesn't want my help, I guess I should mind my own business.
I've been eating food from this world without any concerns about if I would end up stuck here.
In fact, I think I'd be fine with that.
But I wouldn't want to take Ms. Kobayashi away from her world.
Hello, I'm home!
Welcome back.
Oh, you decided to use that?
Yeah, it actually feels pretty amazing.
Ms. Kobayashi...
No means no, Toru!
Calm down.
Why don't you try resting your back against it?
Toru, where have you been all my life? Wow!
Do you want me to adjust anything for you?
No, this is perfectly fine.
So is it everything you want?
I do believe we have a winner.
Well, that's easy enough. Just relax.
I actually feel a lot better.
Are we trading? Do you want me to massage you now?
Oh, uh, sure. Shoulders, please.
What?
Why are your shoulders so tight? Is it because your boobs are heavy?
What are you writing?
It's a grimoire for perception blocking and stuff.
Ah, I love convenient magic.
I was thinking of teaching Kana and Nilulu how to do it first.
You're a good friend to them, Toru.
Oh, you don't need Blattery to have your way with me!
Ugh.
You're so cute when you're shy, but you really don't need to be!
Hm?
I knew it.
Have you ever noticed anything strange about the lines of magic spells and the lines of code and programming?
That they resemble each other?
Yeah.
There's a simple explanation for that.
It's because they were originally conceptualized and developed by mages.
Huh? What, really? I didn't know that.
Are you interested in learning more about this side of things?
If so, then you're probably dying to know.
To know what?
You've been wondering what it was that brought Toru to our world in the first place, have you not?
I can ask Toru about that!
Would you like to know anything about what her family experienced?
Ah!
Is that Toru's father?
Wow, it's been a while.
What are you doing here?
I'm visiting my friend who's in charge.
He's been telling me how Toru's doing.
Is that so?
I assume if you've come here, that you have something to ask me, right?
Yes, that's true.
But, um, just know that I'll also be asking Toru for her perspective.
Hmm.
Very well.
It felt as though we would never find peace.
We did little more than prepare for battles by gathering forces, then clashing against them and wearing ourselves out.
The reason we fought was to defeat the gods and restore the world to a state that was free of any impostors.
We bared our fangs because we hated the thought of being controlled.
And we desperately tried to take back our freedom.
At first, this turmoil is what unified all of the dragons.
But as time drew on, some changed sides that supported the efforts of the gods.
There were others who grew sick of the fighting and refused to lend their aid to either side.
We now refer to the first group as the Harmony Faction.
The others are the Spectator Faction.
And because we were neither, we came to be known as the Chaos Faction.
We are the ones who would plunge the world into chaos.
Our strategy was to fight for several centuries, then wait for several more to build up our strength.
While all of that was happening, I had a child.
Her name was Toru.
She was named after an author from this world.
I'm sorry, I dissociated. What did you say? Something about Toru being named for a human?
That's correct.
This man was here for it all. He used clairvoyance to read that book and write down the text.
He then sold numerous copies of it across our world. It's called plagiarism, I think.
The copyright of an author's works disappears a while after their death, right?
So there's no harm in selling it in another world.
And well before the book is even conceptualized.
I can't live without funds for my research.
Seriously?
Humans.
At the time, I just couldn't regard them with any level of importance.
Occasionally, they'll create amusing knickknacks or design something entertaining.
But that's all I thought they were good for.
There were some among the group who worshipped the gods.
Even though they were nothing compared to the dragons they fought against.
That's why I ignored them as long as I could.
But it became a different story when those humans joined forces with the Harmony faction.
So those in the Chaos faction began spreading the rumor humans were pure evil.
That we were honor bound to destroy.
Papa! Papa! What kind of creatures are humans?
They're nothing but evil.
They should be destroyed.
I thought I had to go along with the faction or else my Toru would be persecuted.
Toru was born into the rigid structure of dragon society with no hope for reform in sight.
And I believed that I had burdened her with a life of being my daughter.
Time to die!
Perhaps I believed she was doomed as a member of my bloodline because of how negative the humans were.
I decided to grant Toru free will over her life.
I wanted her to visit many places, interact with a myriad of beings, and develop her own ideas.
Everything Toru has learned stemmed from an interest curated without bias.
I thought she would eventually come to question the Chaos faction.
Perhaps even challenge their contempt for humans.
But she's completely out of control.
What makes you say that?
Well, for one, she stormed the gods' camp all by herself.
It was there that she was wounded, and then somehow she was able to escape into this world.
That's when I found her in the mountains.
That's correct.
It was quite a surprise.
I never imagined such a strong bond could form between a human and a dragon.
It was fascinating to see for the first time.
So then, why did Toru take that risk?
Her heart.
More than anyone else, Toru wanted to end the fighting.
If she could crush the gods, then the fighting would end.
That must have been what she thought.
Damn.
This is intense.
So now you have the general overview.
You'll have to ask Toru if you want to know her feelings in detail.
Could you tell me one more thing?
I can try.
It's about when I first met Toru.
She had mentioned to me she'd been recently abandoned.
What do you think she meant by that?
Abandoned?
Let me think.
I can hardly surmise Toru's feelings, but I'm sure from your human perspective it sounds like I'm a bad father.
Actually, you're one of the better ones.
Toru was not forced into battle by any faction.
Believe me.
She fought completely of her own volition.
Just as every single dragon did when this first started.
Well, I should be going.
But I want you to know, I will never approve of you two.
Uh...
Yes, sir.
It may be hard to believe in light of current events, but he's made several arrangements with God for her.
Wow.
One more thing.
Take proper care of her until your lifespan runs out.
I'll watch out for her.
I promise.
I'm home.
Welcome back! How was your day today?
Your dad showed up at my office, Toru.
He told me all about what happened before you came here.
So...
I was hoping to hear it from your perspective.
What inspired you to move so far away from your own world?
I'd appreciate it if you told me yourself.
You know, whenever you feel like talking...
It's cool.
You don't have to force yourself.
If you don't want to talk about it, I totally understand.
Promise.
Do you want to know?
Mm-hmm.
There's magic to look like a human?
You did it on the first try?
You really are a genius, aren't you?
Good job.
Your father said he wants you to go to all sorts of places, wherever that may be.
I wonder...
Does the Emperor of Demise want his daughter to become a spectator?
That was that. The day I started my journey.
Humans were everywhere I went.
People are so foolish.
They're fighting today as well.
It's a constant battle over things like land or authority.
But they also create a bunch of interesting things.
That was my first impression.
Well, as a dragon.
Why is it Toru?
I'm Toru.
Toru?
Close enough.
Your name's Kana, isn't it?
You used magic to become a human, too.
Why?
There are lots of exciting things to do with human hands.
I like pranks.
Is that the previous Kana Kamali?
What kind of pranks?
Collecting bugs and stuff.
That's not a real prank.
I want attention from you.
They probably didn't have time for you while they were preparing for battle.
They usually only clash once every few centuries, if at all.
I'm not interested in fighting.
Because you're a coward, Quetzalcoatl.
You're strong but refuse to participate in battles.
I don't like to fight.
What do you want from me?
Looking in from the outside, it's so pointless.
Toru, love.
You should quit the Chaos Faction.
I'm the daughter of the Emperor of Demise.
The representative of the Chaos Faction.
If I were to run, then my father's position would be in jeopardy.
Absurd.
If you can't live your life the way you want, then you fail as a dragon.
The fact that you were put in that position by others must be aggravating.
Is that how it works?
You may be a dragon, but you live too selflessly.
If anyone stands in the way of what you want, kill them.
Even if they're your parents.
That's what dragons do.
Pretty extreme.
Toru.
I can't continue on this journey with you.
We have to end it.
Right.
No hard feelings.
You do make a good point, and I understand what you mean.
I guess it's possible that I've been used by others, too.
I don't agree, of course. I'm not a complete fool.
Prayers are precious resources.
Which is why I think it had felt so good to focus on helping humans.
You got to eat your fill, too.
Thank you, Toru.
I had such fun with you.
I'm glad it was your decision to travel with me.
I'll never forget.
But it wasn't. I couldn't choose anything.
I just... didn't like it. The lack of freedom.
I didn't want the Chaos Faction and Harmony Faction to fight each other.
That was never my will.
It felt good having a friend so close that we could spar.
I respect my father.
But the chains of being the Emperor of Demise's daughter are way too heavy.
I want to live freely. I want to be on my own. I am a dragon. So I'll fight and win my independence.
The factions don't matter. This is my personal fight. I'm going to wipe these guys out and break all the chains clinging to dragons.
I'm going to be free. I'm going to be free. And then... And then...
I didn't have anything. Once I was alone, I found there was nothing I wanted to do.
Being on my own. Being free. Was so... terrifying.
That's how I remember it. I was afraid to be free until you showed up and took my hand. You made me feel like I wasn't alone.
Uh, cool. I was never interested in anything until after I moved to the big city.
I know who I am now.
What?
Miss Kobayashi.
I see that. I've always wanted to be a maid.
Ok so.
What's wrong?
...
OK Iritt
Ms. Kobayashi, I heard they'll be launching fireworks at the summer festival.
Yeah, that's true.
I think my breath would be more amazing, though.
That might turn it into a blood festival.
But the sights you see on the verge of death are so beautiful.
Why are we talking about this?
This week on Who's Rotten?
Scorpio.